At this moment, most companies are truly upgrading to Microsoft Edge and probably I think
because Internet Explorer is no more used, so definitely you don't want to be using Microsoft
Internet Explorer at this moment, because most browsers don't necessarily support it anymore.
But you can't only use Microsoft Intune to deploy Edge to three other devices and Microsoft Office apps.
So, to deploy Microsoft Edge to your devices, if for example on the deploy top Windows 10,
because which Windows 11 is actually pre-installed.
So, what you need to do is the following Windows electronic go to devices.
I'm sorry, apps.
And on the apps we need to go to Windows.
And here you can see we need to try to just click Add.
So, right-click and Add, Windows Celes is Add type Celes.
So, you can see we have for example, we have the Microsoft Edge version.
So, now, later, I'm going to go for the Windows 10 and later, I'm going to click Celes.
So, right-click and Celes, you can see we don't have actually a much too configured here.
You can see the name is going to be microed for Windows 10 and later you can actually change it.
And also, we have category with this productivity.
You can actually change it for example, I can see well I want to pull it for business.
And also, show this as a future app in the company portal.
So, if you've installed the company portal, deploy company portal to Windows 10 or Windows 11 devices,
you want to add to I am, if you want to allow this to be future, I think, I'll say.
So, future app that the user will be able to install it themselves.
You can actually say yes, if no, the app will be deployed to the user's device.
So, let me just select no.
Or, let me just select yes for this.
And then click Nest.
And also, you can see this channel is going to be stable, but we can go for the better audit.
The development channel, but I want to go for this table channel.
And the language is going to be operating system default.
But you can choose or the language if you choice, if you want.
But let's go for the pre-system default.
And in logo, you can see that the beautiful mess of edge logo.
And assignment, here you can see we can see all the devices.
I would mean that all our devices edge would be deployed to a lot of devices.
But it's going to be featured in our company, portal, click Nest, and then create.
So, this profile is going to be created and also what's going to be deployed to all the devices.
But if, for example, we want to deploy microsoft releases from apps, what you need to do is to go to apps.
And on our apps, let's just click Windows Platform.
And then, select, and you can see we have the edge, we just click there right now.
And then, we want to select the microsoft 360 apps, we just turn on later.
You can see, I want to select.
At this moment, you can see also, we don't have so much to configure.
I want to show this in the future, in the company portal.
And I'm going to leave this for productivity.
And here you can just check the information, if they are all correct.
And click Nest.
So, that's what makes this.
Select Office app, which need to be deployed to the devices.
You can see all the different buttons.
You can see, well, at this moment, we don't want to deploy one node or the other deploy
publisher.
We can just select it, or we can decide to select that.
And then, include the Skype for Business.
But Skype for Business is actually a lot of data at this moment.
So, you definitely don't want to deploy it.
Select all the apps, Office apps, at this moment, you need to assume a node.
The visual and the project are totally required.
It uses license to be able to, or probably not to be able to use it.
We also have the 32-bit or 64-bit.
So, you want to go for the 64-bit as saved for some specific users.
Because, for the hardware, work at this moment, there are some users.
So, we are totally required for the 32-bit, because if not, some software they are using
on the device may not work correctly.
Because, that's what it goes hands-in hands with the 32-bit option option.
So, let me go for this default file from one.
You can go for the Office Open Document and the channel.
You can save the one that will install the current channel on that device.
Let's move all our files here.
Yes, for some to install, it should be the latest.
You should come with the exhibition.
It's no, sometimes the share-lock to come with the exhibition means that.
Sometimes the device is being installed.
I shared with this office that has been installed on the device.
It's going to be different than the standard office which you will be installed.
It's going to be using the shared device license, not just on that license, like the E3 or E5.
So, here you can see the one.
You want to have to have a safety of Microsoft's license test on the user as we have.
Install program, save some Microsoft search you bring.
I'll say that you must put that to no.
And then we cannot save the deploy to all devices in our company.
For now, it's a really test environment.
In a production environment, you want to deploy it to just so specific devices.
And then let's click Next.
And then create.
So, by doing that, it's going to take some time.
The apps will now be deployed to all the devices or your Windows 10 or Windows 11 devices.
Your company from that user can start using the apps.